Donald G. Adams Papers, Inclusive: 1962-1980, undated, Bulk: 1972-1977, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1967-1977, undated; 5
  - 62nd Legislature, 1969-1972, undated; 2
    - HR 65, Creating a Special Committee to Study the Volunteer Firemen’s Pension Fund, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - HR 186, In Memory of Clyde E. Smith, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - SB 445, Child Abuse, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - SB 529, Appointing Retired or Active Judges to Sit as Commissioners for the Court of Criminal Appeals, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - 63rd Legislature, 1970-1974, undated; 3
    - General Correspondence and Newsletters, 1971-1972, undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - People to See, 1972, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Job Applications and Requests, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - 62nd Legislature Map and Senate Roster, undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - State Fiscal Year, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Bills from 62nd Second Called Session, HJR 17, SB 1, SB 3, SCR 8, Legislative Rules and Elections, Highway Beautification, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Sabine County Road, 1972, undated (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Sabine River Authority, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Water Contamination and Railroads, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Fish and Game, Forestry, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - County District Issues, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Insurance Issues, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Insurance Law, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Rusk State Hospital, undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Price Discrimination and Oil Marketing, 1972, undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Texas University and College Headcount Enrollment, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - “Texas Labor” Issue, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Department of Public Welfare, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Capital Gains Tax Law, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Death Penalty, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Budget Board, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Recommended General Appropriations Bill for 1974-1975 Biennium (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Recommended General Appropriations Bill for 1974-1975 Biennium (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Legislative Budget Estimates, 1973-1974 Fiscal Year (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Budget Estimates, 1973-1974 Fiscal Year (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Executive Budget, 1974-1975 Biennium, 1973, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - 63rd Legislature, Committee Assignments and Amendments to Senate Rules, 1973, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - 63rd Legislature, Master Legislation List, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Legislation Sent to the Government, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Texas Legislative Council, 9 Proposed Constitutional Amendments Analyzed, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Accomplishments of the 63rd Legislature, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Final Report of the 63rd Legislature, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Education, Correspondence and Reports, 1972, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Texas Education Code, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Texas Public School Finance Plans and Information, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Marijuana Legislation, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Commissioners’ Court Legislation, Nacogdoches and Cherokee Counties, 1973, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - SB 70, Pollution Legislation Information, 1972-1973, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - SB 111, Title III of the Family Code, Analysis, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - SB 120, Unitization for Conservation of Oil and Gas, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - SB 120, Unitization for Conservation of Oil and Gas, Clippings, 1973, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - SB 120, Unitization for Conservation of Oil and Gas, Related Transcripts of Committee Proceedings on Oil Bills, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - SB 120, Unitization for Conservation of Oil and Gas, Bill, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - SB 123, Full Legal Rights to 18-Year-Olds, 1973, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - SB 240, Texas Controlled Substances Act, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - SB 369, HB 447, and HB 750, Pharmacy Bills, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - HJR 5, Texas Constitution Amendment, Majority Age of 18, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Firemen’s Pension Fund Interim Study Subcommittee, 1971-1974, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Hearings before Congressional Subcommittee on Private Pension Plans (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Hearings before Congressional Subcommittee on Private Pension Plans (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - SB 21, Exempting Athletic Organizations from Payment of Limited Sales Tax, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - SB 65, Prohibiting Parole of a Life Sentence for Capital Offenses, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - SB 143, Mabank-Kemp Hospital District, 1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - SB 162, Tuition Fees for Students at State-Supported Institutions, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - SB 164, Relating to a Suit to Determine Paternity of Illegitimate Children, 1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - SB 165, Transporting of Mobile Homes, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - SB 166, Office of District Attorney for the 173rd Judicial District, 1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - SB 167, Criminal District Attorney Office of Kaufman County, 1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - SB 168, Title II Family Code, Correspondence, 1972-1974, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - SB 168, Analyses and Summaries of Title II, “Texas Bar Journal”, 1972-1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - SB 168, Title II Family Code, Committee Report, Amendments, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - SB 168, Title II Family Code, Bill, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - SB 168, Title II Family Code, Bill with Notes, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - SB 168, Title II Family Code, Engrossed Bill, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - SB 172, Veteran’s Day, 1972-1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - SB 173, Private Bird Shooting Area, 1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - SB 235, Transfer of Persons to the Texas Department of Corrections Pending Appeal, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - SB 266, Assistant District Attorney, 2nd Judicial District, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - SB 278, Use of In-Transit License Plates, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - SB 287, Driving While Intoxication (DWI) Testing, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - SB 339, Salaries of Assistants to County School Superintendents, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - SB 361, Authorizing the Board of Regents of Steven F. Austin State University to Sell and Convey Land, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - SB 367, Planning, Constructing, and Operating Bicentennial Expositions, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - SB 381, Reapportionment of Congressional Districts, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - SB 411, Compensation of the District Attorney of the 88th Judicial District, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - SB 452, Experience Requirements for Salary Increments under the Texas State Public Education Compensation Plan, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - SB 513, Rural Fire Protection Plans, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - SB 608, Compensation of Members of the Juvenile Boards of Hardin and Tyler Counties, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - SB 676, State Parklands Passport, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - SB 688, Safety Glazing in Hazardous Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - SB 689, Production of Gas from Common Reservoirs Producing Both Sweet and Sour Gas, 1973, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - SB 716, Blind Assistance Fund, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - SB 893, Commission of Insane Accused Criminals to Rusk State Hospital, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - SB 954, Salaries of the Assistants to the County School Superintendent in Shelby County, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - SB 955, Licensing for Installing and Servicing Certain Alarm Systems, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - SR 138, Amending Senate Rules, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - SR 7-301, Congratulatory and Memorial Resolutions, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - SR 302-502, Congratulatory and Memorial Resolutions, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - SR 503, Creating a Subcommittee for Hearings on the Volunteer Firemen’s Pension Fund, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - SR 504-635, Congratulatory and Memorial Resolutions, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - SR 636-681, Congratulatory and Memorial Resolutions, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - SR 682-833, Congratulatory and Memorial Resolutions, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - SR 848-898, Congratulatory and Memorial Resolutions, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - SCR 22, In Memoriam of Martin Dies, Sr., 1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - SCR 23-25, Allowing Multiple Individuals to Sue the State of Texas, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - SCR 50, Urging Congress to Prohibit Fees for Use of Lakes or Boat Ramps Built with Federal Funds, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - SCR 104, In Appreciation of Ancel Nunn, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - SCR 111, Expressing Thanks to Members of the Medical Community, 1973, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - SJR 35, Limit to Regulate the Terms for Which a Member May be Elected Speaker, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - HB 50, Air Force Training at Midwestern University and Sheppard Technical Training Center, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - SB 38, East Texas Juvenile Board, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Letter to Bill Elmore, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Texas Constitutional Revision Convention, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Proposed Big Thicket Park, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Oil Unitization, Correspondence and Clippings, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Energy Crisis, "Federal Register", 1973 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Healthcare Delivery, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Ed Gunter, Regional Medical Program of Texas, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Ad Valorem Taxes and Masonic Lodges, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Food Stamp Program, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Supplemental Security Income and Welfare Change Over, 1973, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - School Financing, Governor’s Plan, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - 64th Legislature, 1971-1976, undated; 4
    - Proposed Education Bills, Committee on Public Education, 1975, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Adult Education, Correspondence, 1974-1975, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, Correspondence (1 of 3), 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, Correspondence (2 of 3), 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, Correspondence (3 of 3), 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Texans for Equal Rights Amendment, Information and Printed Materials, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Printed Anti-Equal Rights Amendment Materials, 1973-1974, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Committee to Restore Women’s Rights, Anti-Equal Rights Amendment Package, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - SB 14, Juvenile Boards and Probation Programs, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - SB 37, Amending Chapter 16 of the Texas Education Code, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - SB 67, State Funds for Texas State Technical Institute, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - SB 71, Emergency Grants for School Districts, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - SB 77, Mobile Home Seals of Approval, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - SB 80, SB 81, SB 82, SB 597, SB 603, SJR 40, HJR 81, Veterans Issues, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - SB 89, Vehicle Weight Limits, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - SB 90, Employee Retirement System, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - SB 106-108, Criminal Proceedings, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - SB 111, Enforcement of Environmental Bills, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - SB 121, Humane Care and Treatment of Animals, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - SB 124, Regulation of Psychotherapy, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - SB 163, Court Administration, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - SB 168, Workmen’s Compensation Insurance, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - SB 199, Criminal District Attorneys, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - SB 214, Compensation of State Board of Health, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - SB 234-235, Texas Women's University Medical School and Parmer County Hospital District, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - SB 250, Redesignation of Domestic Relations and Special Juvenile Courts, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - SB 251, Compensation for Injured Employees, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - SB 275, Funds Collected or Received by State Agencies, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - SB 286, Texas Occupational Safety Act of 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - SB 300, Related to Voter Registration, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - SB 305-307, Financial and Insurance Institutions, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - SB 323, Amending Insurance Reimbursement, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - SB 344, Amending the Real Estate License Act, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - SB 350 and HB 366, Small Business Assistance, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - SB 388, Interception and Use of Wire or Oral Communications, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - SB 399, Auto Dealer Place Licenses, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - SB 418, Election of Delegates to County and District Party Conventions, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - SB 424, Texas Adult Probation Board, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - SB 432, Amending the Texas Municipal Retirement System Act, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - SB 440, Payment Percentages on Highway Projects, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - SB 443, Requiring Non-Union Employees to Pay Certain Fees, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - SB 445, Requiring License for Activities Relating to the Placement of Children for Adoption, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - SB 449, Providing that Boards of Trustees Consult with Representatives of Teachers, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - SB 453 and 468, Tort Reform, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - SB 469, Licensing and Regulation of Convalescent and Nursing Homes, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - SB 478, Governor’s Public School Plan, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - SB 481-482, Abortion Issues, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - SB 490, Insurance Companies under the Non-Profit Corporation Act, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - SB 491, Amendment of Insurance Code (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - SB 491, Amendment of Insurance Code (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - SB 496, Industrial Accident Board Confidentiality, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - SB 498, Appointment of a Qualified Retired Judge to Sit for a Regular Judge, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - SB 503, State Support for Local Bicentennial Projects, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - SB 522, Penalties for Possession of Marijuana, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - SB 524, Natural Gas Conservation Act of 1975 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - SB 525, Qualification of Applicants for Licensure to Practice Medicine, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - SB 528, SB 530, and SB 561, Definitions of Peace Officers, Dentistry, and Newspapers, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - SB 567, Amending Duties and Responsibilities of County and Probate Judges Pertaining to Estates and Wards, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - SB 611, Regulation of Practice of Optometry, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - SB 635, Texas Patients’ Insurance Compensation Board, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - SB 640, North Texas Municipal Water District, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - SB 670, Licensing and Regulation of Speech Pathologists and Audiologists, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - SB 721, State Historical Marker Program, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - SB 725, State Office of Early Childhood Development, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - SB 733, Related to Payment of Wages, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - SB 752, Filing Title Transfer on Used Cars, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - SB 792, Regulation of Clinical Laboratories Personnel, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - SB 812, Regulating Practice of Social Work, 1975, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - SB 815 and SB 817, Salaries of District Clerks, 1975, undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - SB 821, Prescription Requirement for Hearing Aid, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - SB 830 and SB 834, Evidence Admissibility and Licensing of Child Care Facilities, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - SB 837, Regulation, Licensing, and Taxing of Horse Racing and Pari-Mutual Wagering, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - SB 863, Relating to a Lien for the Care, Feed, and Maintenance of Domestic Animals, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - SB 867, Fees and Service Charges for Issuing License Receipts, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - SB 869, Taxation and Regulation of the Coin-Operated Machine Industry, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - SB 872, Board of Managers of the Texas State Railroad, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - SB 888, Establishment, Administration, and Enforcement of Countywide Appraisals of Property, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - SB 892, Amendment of the Statute of Frauds, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - SB 940, Chartering, Regulation, and Supervision of Credit Unions, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - SB 965, Regulation of Child Care Facilities, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - SB 986, Texas Amusement Machine Commission, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - SB 989, Relating to Recording the Consideration for Transfers of Real Property, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - SB 1009, Civil Liability of Governmental Units, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - SB 1018, County Clerk and Recorder Fees, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - SB 1024, Regulation of Certain Healthcare Facilities and Services, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - SB 1026, Relating to Prohibition of Electronic Bugging Devices, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - SB 1054 and SB 1057, Gulf Coast Waste Disposal and Pretrial Release and Bail, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - SR 727, Commendation of Texas Legislative Service, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - SR 729, Commendation of Texas Senate Floor Personnel, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - SCR 17 and SR 76, Legislative Rules, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - SJR 3, State and Local Retirement Systems, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - SJR 10, Right of Appeal for the State in Criminal Cases, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - SJR 11, Introduced Version, 10 Amendments to Texas Constitution, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - SJR 11, 8 Amendments to Texas Constitution, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - SJR 11, Accompanying Documents, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - SJR 22, SJR 31-32, SJR 34, SJR 37-38, SJR 49, Constitutional Amendments, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - HB 29, Restricting Phone Solicitation, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - HB 42, Group Marketing of Motor Vehicle Insurance, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - HB 69, Allowing Cities to Bring Suit for Collection of Delinquent City Taxes, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - HB 82, Clergymen, Penitent Privilege, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - HB 108-110, Tax Rate for Natural Gas, Damages for Wrongful Death, Licensing for Tractors, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - HB 139, Speed Limits, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - HB 147, Prohibiting Using Live Animals in Dog Races or Dog Coursing, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - HB 163, Saturday and Sunday Closing Laws, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - HB 165, Employee Retirement System of Texas, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - HB 226, County School Administration, 1975, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - HB 234, Number of Days in School Year, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - HB 244, Prohibiting Acts by or Relating to Strikebreakers, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - HB 247, Texas State Board of Examiners in Social Psychotherapy, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - HB 254, Establishing Texas Women’s University Medical School, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - HB 292, Certificate of Title for Transfer of or Security Interests in Motorboats and Outboard Motors, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - HB 350, Texas Commission on the Status of Women, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - HB 373, Licensing and Regulation of Nurses Aids, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - HB 382, Licensing and Regulation of Speech Pathologists and Audiologists, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - HB 383, Enabling a Home-Rule City to Appoint an Environmental Health Officer, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - HB 419, Providing Boards of Trustees Consult with Representatives of Teachers and Auxiliary Personnel, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - HB 420, Amending Chapter 16 of the Texas Education Code, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - HB 431, Revising the Private Investigators and Private Security Agencies Act, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - HB 437, Relating to the Registration and Regulation of Architects, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - HB 498, Allocating Tax Funds to the Available School Fund, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - HB 510, Division of Occupational Safety, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - HB 512, Prohibition of Discrimination in Motor Vehicle Insurance Rates, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - HB 546, Revision of Tax Laws, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - HB 549, Sale of Cherokee County Land by the Texas Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - HB 560, False, Misleading, and Deceptive Trade Practices, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - HB 565, Regulation of Certain Child Care Facilities, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - HB 608, Establishment of Standards of Construction, Maintenance, and Operation of County Jail Facilities, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - HB 626, Number of Instruction Days in the School Year, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - HB 633, Regulation of Banks, Trust Companies, and Bank Holding Companies, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - HB 634, Driver Education Programs in Schools, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - HB 657, Energy Tax, Texas Energy Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - HB 657 and HB 1991, Energy Tax, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - HB 660, Imposition, Implementation, and Administration of a Corporate Profits Tax, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - HB 707, Prohibition of the Appointment of Convicted Felons as Peace Officers, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - HB 733, Disclosures in the Disposition or Offer of Certain Subdivided Land, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - HB 768, Qualification of Certain Applicants for Licensure to Practice Medicine, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - HB 819, Public Utility Regulatory Act, Draft, 1975, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - HB 819, Public Utility Regulatory Act, Bill, 1975, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - HB 819, Public Utility Regulatory Act, Bill Comparisons, 1975, undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - HB 1126, Public School Financing, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - HB 1535, Valuation of Open-Space Land Used for Agricultural Purposes, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - HB 201, Amending Title II Family Code, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - HB 225, Child Care Facility Act, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - HCR 100, Imported Fire Ant Eradication Funds, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Pension and Fiscal Data, Firefighter Pension Fund, 1976, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General Opinions on Firefighter Pension Reform, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - General Pension Information, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - General Pension Information, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - General Pension Information, 1974-1975, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Conference Report, Employee Retirement Income Security Act, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Bill Establishing Actuarially Sound State Retirement Systems, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - State and Local Government Retirement Systems, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Retirement Systems for Employees of State and Local Governments, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Federal Pension and Disclosure Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Qualifications for Pension Systems, 1968-1975, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Actuarial Analysis, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - SB 702, Information Gathering, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - SB 702, Correspondence between City Officials and Dick Brown, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 6)